

# Ramsay Shiells



Software Developer



Inverurie, Scotland

#### **Profile**

Software Developer with 5+ years of experience. Passionate about learning and exploring new technologies and I believe in producing clear and concise code in well structured applications. I also like cooking, gaming, playing the guitar, skiing and running.

### **Experience**

## **Software Developer - Evolve Ltd**

- March 2014 Present
- Designing, implementing and testing features in existing and new applications
- Maintaining and fixing bugs in historical applications
- Producing documentation
- Creating releases
- Supporting and mentoring Graduate Software Developers

#### **Graduate Software Developer - Evolve Ltd** September 2012 - March 2014

- Designing, implementing and testing features in existing applications
- Maintaining and fixing bugs in historical applications
- Customer Support and Operational Support

## Ski Instructor & Attendant - Alford Ski Centre August 2004 - May 2015

- Instructing children and adults from beginner to expert level
- Maintenance of the dry ski slope and equipment
- Taking bookings and payments

#### **Education**

### **MSc Cloud Computing - Aberdeen University** September 2011 - September 2012

"Creating, Publishing and Visualising Data for the Semantic Web" MSc Project in collaboration with IBM

#### **BSc Hons Computing Science - Aberdeen University** September 2008 - September 2011

"Making Linked Data Accessible" Honours Project in collaboration with Aberdeen City Council

## **Projects**

**Android App - Grampian Transport Museum January 2017 - March 2017** 

Application used to supplement exhibits with images and videos

#### **Details**

**13-02-1988** 

ramsayshiells@me.com

www.ramsayshiells.info

## **Programming Languages**

Js Javascript 日 HTML

SQL

🖺 Java

**E** CSS

PHP

**◎** C#

#### **Frameworks**

Alfresco

Spring

dōjō Dojo

React

JQuery

🕞 Redux

Android SDK

**∼** .NET

#### **Tools**

Eclipse

Maven

Microsoft SQL Server

M TFS

★ Atom

🛴 MySQL

**G** Github